{
    "lessons": [
        {
            "category": "Basics",
            "flashcards": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "word": "你好",
                "pinyin": "nǐ hǎo",
                "translation": "Hello"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "word": "谢谢",
                "pinyin": "xiè xie",
                "translation": "Thank you"
            }
            ],
            "quizzes": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "How do you say 'Hello' in Mandarin?",
                "options": ["你好","谢谢"],
                "answer": "你好"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "What is the translation of '谢谢'?",
                "options": ["Goodbye","Thank you"],
                "answer": "Thank you"
            }
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Advanced",
            "flashcards": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "word": "对不起",
                "pinyin": "duì bu qǐ",
                "translation": "Sorry"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "word": "请问",
                "pinyin": "qǐng wèn",
                "translation": "Excuse me"
            }
            ],
            "quizzes": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "How do you say 'Sorry' in Mandarin?",
                "options": ["对不起","请问"],
                "answer": "对不起"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "What is the pinyin for '请问'?",
                "options": ["qǐng wèn","duì bu qǐ"],
                "answer": "qǐng wèn"
            }
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Numbers",
            "flashcards": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "word": "一",
                "pinyin": "yī",
                "translation": "One"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "word": "二",
                "pinyin": "èr",
                "translation": "Two"
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "word": "三",
                "pinyin": "sān",
                "translation": "Three"
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "word": "四",
                "pinyin": "sì",
                "translation": "Four"
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "word": "五",
                "pinyin": "wǔ",
                "translation": "Five"
            },
            {
                "id": 6,
                "word": "六",
                "pinyin": "liù",
                "translation": "Six"
            },
            {
                "id": 7,
                "word": "七",
                "pinyin": "qī",
                "translation": "Seven"
            }
            ],
            "quizzes": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "How do you say 'Three' in Mandarin?",
                "options": ["三","五"],
                "answer": "三"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "What is the translation of '六'?",
                "options": ["Four","Six"],
                "answer": "Four"
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": "What is the pinyin for '五'?",
                "options": ["sān","wǔ"],
                "answer": "wǔ"
            }
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Days",
            "flashcards": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "word": "星期一",
                "pinyin": "xīng qī yī",
                "translation": "Monday"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "word": "星期二",
                "pinyin": "xīng qī èr",
                "translation": "Tuesday"
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "word": "星期三",
                "pinyin": "xīng qī sān",
                "translation": "Wednesday"
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "word": "星期四",
                "pinyin": "xīng qī sì",
                "translation": "Thursday"
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "word": "星期五",
                "pinyin": "xīng qī wǔ",
                "translation": "Friday"
            },
            {
                "id": 6,
                "word": "星期六",
                "pinyin": "xīng qī liù",
                "translation": "Saturday"
            },
            {
                "id": 7,
                "word": "星期天",
                "pinyin": "xīng qī tiān",
                "translation": "Sunday"
            }
            ],
            "quizzes": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "How do you say 'Monday' in Mandarin?",
                "options": ["星期一","星期天"],
                "answer": "星期一"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "What is the translation of '星期五'?",
                "options": ["Friday","Wednesday"],
                "answer": "Friday"

            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": "What is the pinyin for '星期天'?",
                "options": ["xīng qī tiā","xīng qī yī"],
                "answer": "xīng qī tiān"
            }
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Months",
            "flashcards": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "word": "一月",
                "pinyin": "yī yuè",
                "translation": "January"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "word": "二月",
                "pinyin": "èr yuè",
                "translation": "February"
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "word": "三月",
                "pinyin": "sān yuè",
                "translation": "March"
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "word": "四月",
                "pinyin": "sì yuè",
                "translation": "April"
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "word": "五月",
                "pinyin": "wǔ yuè",
                "translation": "May"
            },
            {
                "id": 6,
                "word": "六月",
                "pinyin": "liù yuè",
                "translation": "June"
            },
            {
                "id": 7,
                "word": "七月",
                "pinyin": "qī yuè",
                "translation": "July"
            }
            ],
            "quizzes": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "How do you say 'January' in Mandarin?",
                "options": ["一月","七月"],
                "answer": "一月"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "What is the translation of '五月'?",
                "options": ["May","June"],
                "answer": "May"
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": "What is the pinyin for '六月'?",
                "options": ["liù yuè","wǔ yuè"],
                "answer": "liù yuè"
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "question": "How do you say 'April' in Mandarin?",
                "options": ["四月","三月"],
                "answer": "四月"
            }
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Colors",
            "flashcards": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "word": "红色",
                "pinyin": "hóng sè",
                "translation": "Red"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "word": "蓝色",
                "pinyin": "lán sè",
                "translation": "Blue"
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "word": "绿色",
                "pinyin": "lǜ sè",
                "translation": "Green"
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "word": "黄色",
                "pinyin": "huáng sè",
                "translation": "Yellow"
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "word": "黑色",
                "pinyin": "hēi sè",
                "translation": "Black"
            },
            {
                "id": 6,
                "word": "白色",
                "pinyin": "bái sè",
                "translation": "White"
            },
            {
                "id": 7,
                "word": "橙色",
                "pinyin": "chéng sè",
                "translation": "Orange"
            }
            ],
            "quizzes": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "How do you say 'Red' in Mandarin?",
                "options": ["红色","蓝色"],
                "answer": "红色"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "What is the translation of '白色'?",
                "options": ["White","Black"],
                "answer": "White"
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": "What is the pinyin for '绿色'?",
                "options": ["lǜ sè","huáng sè"],
                "answer": "lǜ sè"
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "question": "How do you say 'Blue' in Mandarin?",
                "options": ["蓝色","绿色"],
                "answer": "蓝色"
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "question": "What is the translation of '橙色'?",
                "options": ["Orange","Red"],
                "answer": "Orange"
            }
            ]
        }
    ]   
}
  